<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cancer Research on xiaoni&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://xiaonilee.github.io/tags/cancer-research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cancer Research on xiaoni&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiaonilee.github.io/tags/cancer-research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bioinformatics analysis of prognostic value of PITX1 gene in breast cancer</title>
      <link>https://xiaonilee.github.io/post/bioscirep/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiaonilee.github.io/post/bioscirep/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The present study assessed the correlation between &lt;strong&gt;PITX1&lt;/strong&gt; expression and the prognostic factor of &lt;strong&gt;breast cancer&lt;/strong&gt; by using various online analysis databases to explore the prognostic significance of PITX1 gene in the treatment of breast cancer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Herein, I will recover all figures for this paper step by step.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Bioinformatics Analysis of Tumor-Infiltrating Immune Cells</title>
      <link>https://xiaonilee.github.io/post/tumorimmune/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiaonilee.github.io/post/tumorimmune/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Recent clinical successes of cancer immunotherapy necessitate the investigation of the interaction between malignant cells and the host immune system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Herein, I summarized five bioinformatics tools for comprehensive analysis of tumor-infiltrating immune cells.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identification of Therapeutic Targets and Prognostic Biomarkers Among CXC Chemokines in the Renal Cell Carcinoma Microenvironment</title>
      <link>https://xiaonilee.github.io/post/frontoncol/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiaonilee.github.io/post/frontoncol/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this study, the authors conducted an in-depth and comprehensive bioinformatics analysis of the expression of &lt;strong&gt;CXC chemokines&lt;/strong&gt; in &lt;strong&gt;Renal cell carcinoma&lt;/strong&gt;  and evaluated their potential as therapeutic targets and prognostic biomarkers based on several large public databases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Herein, I will recover all figures for this paper step by step.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
